videosecrets.com 2016-05-05

# Flirt4Free Privacy Policy

### What Personal Information About Customers Does Affiliates Flirt4free Gather?

**Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future visits for you, improving our services, and communicating with you.

**Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Affiliates Flirt4free. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Due to the sensitive issues involving access to adult content by children, we do not permit access to our sites from these anonymous services.

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login name; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed; services you visited; your customer service history, and phone number used to call our 800 number.

* * *

### What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as "What's New".

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Flirt4Free' coolest services, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

* * *

### Does Affiliates Flirt4free Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our affiliates is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries Affiliates Flirt4free, controls and as described below.

**Agents:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments in real time, sending e-mail notifications or updates, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but they do not have our authorization to use it for other purposes.

**Promotional Offers:** Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Flirt4Free affiliates on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please send email to [customerservice@vsmedia.com](mailto:customerservice@vsmedia.com)

**Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy sites or assets. In such transactions, affiliate information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Flirt4Free, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, affiliate information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

**Protection of Affiliates Flirt4free and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Affiliates Flirt4free, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

* * *

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your account passwords and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

* * *

### What Information Can I Access?

Affiliates Flirt4free gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.

Your Account Information

* * *

### What Choices Do I Have?

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please send email to [customerservice@vsmedia.com](mailto:customerservice@vsmedia.com) (If you do not want to receive Terms and Conditions and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of Affiliates Flirt4free, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use such services as Affiliates Flirt4free and other live shows if you do not use cookies.

In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, Site Seeing on the Internet <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee/index.html>.

* * *

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Affiliates Flirt4free, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. If you have any concern about privacy at Affiliates Flirt4free, please send us a thorough description to [sales@flirt4free.com](mailto:sales@flirt4free.com), and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms and Conditions will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

* * *

### Opt-Out Instructions

If you do not wish to receive emails about our service please use one of the following means to remove yourself. We certainly do not wish to market to anyone who doesn't want it!

**Online:**Contact Management

**Toll Free:** 1-800-685-9236 (USA only)

**Int'l Phone:** 1-818-880-9021 (USA only)

**Email:**[sales@flirt4free.com](mailto:sales@flirt4free.com)

**Regular Mail:**

  * VS Media Inc.
  * 4607 Lakeview Canyon Rd.#338
  * Westlake Village, CA 91361
